等一下
Hold on a second.
好球…
Nice.
有东西给你
I got you something.
这什么东西？
What's this?
812块钱
Eight hundred and twelve bucks.
老里奥没跟你说吗 跟我过夜…
Didn't Big Leon tell you? It's a thousand...
…可要一千块钱才够
...to have me for the whole night.
这是干什么呀？
What's this for?
我现在有赚钱了
Well,I'm making money now.
这是要还你帮我付的电费 跟数不清的披萨的钱
I'm paying you back for headshots,electric bills,all that pizza....
我爱你
I love you,man.
谢了，老兄 我有钱可以买小马了
Well,thanks,man. Now I can get my pony.
这是我小小的心意…
This is a little extra something for...
…谢谢你平日的照顾
...always being there for me.
我不晓得该说什么了
Wow,I don't know what to say.
怎么样？
What do you say?
我不知道
I don't know.
这是个手镯吧？
It's a bracelet.
上头还刻了字，你看看
Isn't it? It's engraved,too. Check it out.
“我的好兄弟”
"To my best bud."
谢了，好兄弟
Thanks,best bud.
戴上去啊
Put it on.
现在吗？
Now?
不…这么美的东西 应该留到特殊的场合再戴
No,it should be saved for a special occasion.
不…妙就妙在这里 这配什么都好看
No,that's the beauty part. It goes with everything.
老兄，你戴起来简直太合适了
When you put this on,you're good to go.
我从没这么合适过，所以为何不试试戴首饰呢对吧
I've never been "good to go, "so why not try some jewelry, huh?
天啊
Oh,man!
真是太配你了
You are so wearing that bracelet!
可不是嘛！
I so am!
你知道这对你的性生活 有什么样的影响吗？
Any idea what this will do for your sex life?
刚开始时说不定会让我慢半拍
It might slow down at first,but...
等到习惯这个重量之后 就会让我重振雄风了
...once I'm used to the extra weight,I'll be back on track.
六人行 第2季 第14集 高中舞会录影带
The One With the Prom Video
看起来很好 那就好了
-This all looks good. -Great.
如果我要打电话询问 你以前的经验呢？
If I want to call for a reference on your last job...?
就写在下面了 我经理叫做钱德宾
That's right there,see? The manager,Chandler Bing?
好吧
All right.
来看看你是不是跟你写的 一样好，做一份沙拉来瞧瞧
Let's see if you're as good in person as you are on paper. Make me a salad.
沙拉？ 其实我可以做些难度比较高的
A salad? I could do something more complicated.
不用，沙拉就行了
No,just the salad will be fine.
没问题
You got it.
可是我要你一边做 一边告诉我你正在做什么
Now I want you to tell me what you're doing while you're doing it.
好，我在撕生菜
All right. Well,I'm tearing the lettuce.
菜脏吗？
Is it dirty?
不…别担心，我待会儿会洗
Oh,I'm gonna wash it.
别洗，我喜欢脏的
Don't. I like it dirty.
你说了算
That's your call.
好，你接下来要做什么？
So,what are you going to do next?
我想，我接下来要切蕃茄了
I thought that l'd cut up the tomatoes.
蕃茄结实吗？
Are they firm?
还可以啦
They're okay.
你确定蕃茄没坏？
You sure they haven't gone bad?
你确定没有非常非常的坏？
You sure they're not very,very bad?
是啊，还可以啦
No,really,they're okay.
你会切得很漂亮吗？
You gonna slice them up real nice?
事实上，我打算切成丝状
I was going to do them julienne.
我要走了
I'm out of here!
喂？
Hello?
不，瑞秋现在不在 你要不要留话？
Rachel's not here. Can I take a message?
好，哪个凯西…？
How do we spell Casey?
是《击球手凯西》里的凯西 还是“KC和阳光乐队”的凯西？
Is it like "at the bat" or "and The Sunshine Band"?
这个凯西是什么人啊？
Hey,who's this Casey?
她看电影认识的人
A guy she met at the movies.
真的？他找她干什么？
What does he want with her?
我猜他想跟她跳点小舞…
I guess he wants to do a little dance...
…做一点小爱…
...you know,make a little love....
今天晚上就把她“解决”掉
Well,get down tonight.
我不知道，我不懂…
I don't know. I don't
两个月前 我们就差这么一点点了
I don't get it! Two months ago,Rachel and I were this close.
现在呢 我在替她看电影认识的人留言
Now I'm taking messages from guys she meets at the movies?
应该是 这个凯西替我留言才对呀
I mean,this Casey should be taking down my messages,you know?
或…或是… 或是我跟瑞秋应该在一起…
Or Rachel and I should be together...
…然后我们… 我们一起请电话秘书
...and we should get some kind of message service.
耐心点吧，会有那一天的
Hang in there. It's gonna happen.
好，你怎么知道呢？
Now,how do you know that?
因为她是你的龙虾
Because she's your lobster.
她有话要说的
Oh,she's going somewhere.
谁不晓得龙虾一旦恋爱 就会白头偕老呢
It's a known fact that lobsters fall in love and mate for life.
你真的可以看到老龙虾夫妻…
You know what? You can actually see old lobster couples...
…在水缸里爪子牵着爪子散步
...walking around their tank,holding claws,like....
你必须想象出龙虾的样子
You have to picture lobsters.
好点了吗？
Hey,you feeling better?
我想我的第五次澡 终于洗掉那个面试了
Yeah,I think that fifth shower got the interview off me.
你还有其他的机会吗？
Do you have other possibilities?
有，我很可能会付不出房租来
There is the possibility that I won't make rent.
莫妮卡，你要的话我可以借你钱
If you want,I can lend you money.
如果我没有办法马上还 看到你就会内疚跟紧张
If I couldn't pay you back right away,I'd feel guilty and tense around you.
好吧 那你为什么不跟爸妈借呢？
Then why not borrow it from Mom and Dad?
反正你看到他们 就会内疚跟紧张
You feel guilty and tense around them already.
还不如趁机会跟他们要点钱
Might as well make some money off of them.
他说得很有道理
The man's got a point.
什么东西亮亮的？
What is that sparkly thing?
那个？那个是…
That thing?
是…有点俗气啦
Yeah,it's a little flashy.
不俗气
No,no.
不会…对道上兄弟来讲不会
No,no. It's not flashy. Not for a goodfella.
天呐 真时髦 你一定花了不少达布隆（古西班牙金币）吧？
Man,that is sharp! That must have cost you quite a few doubloons.
真有趣，就好像嘉宝姐妹（匈牙利歌手）其中之一
It's fun. It's like knowing one of the Gabor sisters.
亲爱的
Hi,darling.
这是什么？
What's this?
你以前的东西
Some of your old stuff.
亲爱的，我们要给你一个惊喜
Well,sweetie,we have a surprise for you.
你房间要改成健身房了
We're turning your room into a gym.
的确是个惊喜
Wow,that is a surprise!
只有个小问题 为何不挑罗斯的房间？
Just one question. Why not Ross's room?
那我们也讨论过了…
We talked about that...
…但你哥哥有那么多的科学奖杯 奖牌，还有优点勋章…
... but your brother had so many science trophies,plaques,merit badges....
我们不想去惊动它们
We didn't want to disturb them.
上帝也不准
God forbid!
有什么新消息吗？有什么可以告诉我们的？工作怎么样？
What's new? What can you tell us?How's your job?
我的工作？哦…
My job? Well....
我有没有提过我还没男朋友？
Did I mention I still don't have a boyfriend?
哦，我只是在假装而已
Oh well. I just assumed.
-哦，嗨，瑞秋！-嗨
-Oh, hi, Rachel! -Hi.
我们很遗憾你父母分开的消息
We were so sorry to hear about your parents splitting up.
他们只是分居 谁知道呢，看看吧
Well,they're just separated. You never know! We'll see.
老实说，我们一点也不惊讶
I can't say any of us were surprised.
从我们认识他们开始 他们就一直很不快乐
They've been unhappy ever since we've known them.
特别是在夏威夷那件事之后
Especially after that incident in Hawaii.
哪件事啊？
What? What incident?
没什么啦… 一定是我想到别人去了
No,no. I must be thinking of someone else.
或许是我
Maybe me!
你不是要叠衣服吗？
Don't you have some folding to do?
快去吧，去叠呀
Fold. You fold.
还要再加一点吗？ 不用了，谢谢
-Want a refill? -I'm all right,thanks.
你得再给我一点时间 我要学得逼真一点
Give me a second. I want to get this just right.
老兄啊，十一点方向 有个火辣女O在看着你
Dude,eleven o'clock,totally hot babe checking you out.
学得很不错 我想我可以去变性了
That was really good. I think I'm ready for my penis now.
我知道你在想什么 戴维托马斯，温迪快餐的创办人，对吧？
I know what you're thinking. Dave Thomas,founder of Wendy's.
我叫盖儿
I'm Gail.
我真的必须走了 很高兴认识你
I really have to go,but it was nice meeting you.
真是太好了
Excellent!
他可以送我录影机 或是一套高尔夫球具也可以
He could have gotten me a VCR or a set of golf clubs.
但他就送了我一个“排斥女人”的东西
But no! He got me the "woman repeller"!
莱伯瑞斯家族的眼中钉（钢琴家，生前是同性恋，死于艾滋病）
The eyesore from the Liberace House of Crap!
没那么惨啦 对，你当然说得容易了
-It's not bad. -Easy for you to say.
你又不用走来走去炫耀怪头都不要的废品
You're not sporting a reject from the Mr. Tcollection!
“我可怜戴着首饰的笨蛋”
"l pity the fool that puts on my jewelry! I do! I do!"
“我可怜戴着…”
"l pity that fool"
兄弟，我们正在玩… 名人模仿秀呢
Hey,man! We were just doing some impressions.
你也表演一下马塞尔・马索（哑剧大师）吧
Do your Marcel Marceau.
模仿得很像呢
That's actually good.
你看看那个家伙
Would you look at that guy?
他跟她已经说了多久了？
How long has he been talking to her?
-几分钟吧 -那就再加倍吧
-A couple minutes.-Try doubling that.
滚开吧，兄弟 她只是服务生，又不是艺妓
It's like,back off,buddy! She's a waitress,not a geisha.
我想她没有关系吧
I think she's okay.
你看看…
Look at that!
你看她把他推开，他还不滚
She pushes him away and he won't budge!
我要采取行动了
I'm gonna do something.
我们可以在山上…
We'll get a condo...
…租个公寓 滑进滑出，棒透了
... right on the mountain. Ski in,ski out,it's great.
对不起，你是瑞秋吗？
Excuse me? Are you Rachel?
什么？
What?
我叫罗斯盖勒
Ross Geller.
广告里说你很漂亮，但是…哇
God,in your ad you said you were pretty,but wow!
你…你在干嘛？
What are you doing?
老天，不是今天吗？
Oh,my God,is this the wrong day?
我真不敢相信
I don't believe it!
这件事如果成了的话 将来跟孙子们就有话讲了
If it works out,we'll have something to tell the grandkids!
对呀
You sure will.
对了，我该走了
I've gotta go.
保重了
Take care.
慢走，再见
See you later.
不客气
You're welcome.
什么？ 我是在救你呀
-What? -I was saving you.
救我？让我不用 跟有趣的男人愉快地交谈？
Saving me from a pleasant conversation with an interesting man?
从我坐的那边看起来…
From where I was
罗斯，你现在听我说
Okay,Ross,listen to me.
我不是要你救的人
I am not yours to save.
但是你是呀
But you are.
什么？
What?
你是我的龙虾
You're my lobster.
你知道吗？ 你又在装跟我盲目约会了
Are you being the blind-date guy again?
不…你是…你是我的龙虾
No,you're my lobster.
龙虾…
Lobsters....
…在水缸里，老的时候
In the tank,when they're old...
…它们会… 它们爪牵爪散步
...they get with the They walk around holding the claws.
在水缸里…
In the tank! You know,with...
…爪子牵着爪子…
...with the holding and....
菲比，帮我解释一下 龙虾的事，好不好？
Pheebs,you wanna help me with the lobster thing?
再表演一次爪子
Do the claws again.
瑞秋，忘了龙虾的事吧
Rach,forget the lobsters,okay?
我们…那我们呢？
Let's talk What about us?
罗斯，没有“我们”
Ross,there is no "us," okay?
你听我说
No! Listen to me!
我爱上了你，然后我受伤了
I fell for you and I get clobbered.
然后你爱上我 结果我还是受伤了
You then fall for me and I again get clobbered.
我受够了伤害
I'm tired of being clobbered,you know?
根本就不值得
It's just not worth it.
但是…但…
Well,but
没有“但是”了，罗斯
No "but," Ross.
我们是永远不可能的，接受吧
We are never gonna happen,okay? Accept that.
除非什么呢？
Except that what?
不…
No. No.
接受吧
Accept that.
我必须得走了
I gotta go.
老兄，你看，我的好兄弟 你好吗？
Hey,man! Look,it's my best bud! How you doing?
你这个马塞尔・马索真是模仿得越来越好了
You're getting good at that Marcel Marceau thing.
乔伊，我们去打球，怎么样？ 你跟我，你说怎么样啊？
What do you say we play some ball? You and me,huh?
是我不好
Okay,that's my bad.
你要是那么讨厌那只手镯 你应该直说就可以了
If you hated the bracelet,you should have just said so.
我戴着这么讨厌的手镯…
Doesn't the fact that I wore it...
…那不就证明了我有多么重视 我们之间的友谊了吗？
...say how much our friendship means to me?
那你侮辱这只手镯 还有你嘲笑我的那件事呢？
But you insulted the bracelet and you made fun of me.
所以说，我是个混蛋嘛
Well,that's the part where I'm a wank.
不过我希望 你不要往那个方向想，好吗？
I was hoping you wouldn't focus on that.
是吗，那么看看这个
Oh, yeah?. Well, focus on this.
很难去评论这个
Hard to argue with that.
你不要这样嘛 我已经向你道过一百次歉了
Come on,man! I said I was sorry a hundred times.
我保证以后手镯不离…
I promise,I will never take it off my...
…手
...wrist.
如果你要留在那里生气的话…
But if you want to stay in there and be mad...
…那你就留在里面好了
...you just,you stay in there.
你知道吗…
You know what the
我向你下跪了…
I am here,on my knees...
…我举着这些沙发垫子…
... holding up these couch cushions...
…表示我对你的歉意还有悔恨
...as a symbol of my sorrow and regret.
跟圣经时代的人一样
Much like they did in biblical times.
你现在虽然很生气…
Though you may haveth anger now....
你还会为你自己辩论的对吧
You're gonna grab yourself again,aren't you?
格拉芙（网球运动员）又吐口水了
You know,that Steffi Graf has quite a tush.
说说而已嘛，就在电视上
I'm just saying! It's right there!
各位
Hey,guys.
亲爱的
Hi,darling.
我孙子呢？你没有带他来啊？
You didn't bring my grandson?
不，他在…卡萝跟苏珊那儿
He's at Carol and Susan's today.
我公司有一个女同性恋
A woman in my office is a lesbian.
说说而已
I'm just saying!
杰克，你看 你觉得很好笑的油漆广告来了
Jack,look! There's that house paint commercial that cracks you up!
你到哪儿去了？ 人间炼狱
-Where have you been? -Emotional hell.
他们有没有借给你钱？
Did they lend you the money?
没有，我还没有开口
No,I haven't asked them yet.
去呀，莫妮卡，说呀
Come on,Monica,do it.
爸，妈
Hey,you guys.
莫妮卡有事要找你们
Monica has some news.
抱歉我以前没有告诉你们…
So listen,I'm sorry I didn't tell you this before,but...
…我现在…并没有在工作 因为我必须离职
... I'm no longer at my job. I had to leave it.
为什么？
Why?
公司要求我的
Because they made me.
你被炒鱿鱼 那你现在怎么办呢？
You were fired? What are you gonna do?
茱蒂，放心啦 这可是我们的小莫妮卡宝贝儿
Judy,relax. This is our little Harmonica we're talking about.
我们教导有方
We taught her well.
薪水的百分之十上哪儿去了？ 存银行了
-Ten percent of your paycheck goes? -ln the bank.
就是嘛，所以她在吃她的老本 存钱本来就是应急的
So she dips into her savings. That's what it's there for.
她不会有事的，对吗，亲爱的
She's gonna be fine.Aren't you, sweetie?
在银行里
In the bank.
如果那些钱还不够用的话…
If you need a little extra...
…你知道哪里有钱啊
...you know where to find it.
有大张一点的吗？
Anything larger back there?
我真不敢相信
I can't believe it!
你停一下，好不好？
Would you stop already?
不要再怨天尤人了，高兴一点
Get out of the bitter barn and play in the hay.
你说得对，我应该高兴一点的
Oh,you're right. I should play in the hay.
忘了我刚才花四百块钱去买一个我恨的手镯这件事
I just dropped $400 to replace a bracelet I hated to begin with.
逗我开心啊
Bring on the hay!
嘿
Hey!
我这儿有个使你快乐的东西
I've got something that'll make you happy.
猜猜甘瑟刚找到什么了？
Guess what Gunther found?
你现在有两个了
Hey,now you have two!
Oh,now you have two.
我该如何是好？
What am I gonna do?
你怎么有两个？
How come you have two?
这个是送你的
This one's for you.
少来了
Get out!
我没办法
No,I can't.
我知道这对你的意义重大…
I know how much this means to you...
…我也知道这不只是首饰而已
...and this is about more than jewelry.
这是关于你跟我 还有我们是“好兄弟”
It's about you and me and the fact that we're "best buds."
这叫友谊吗？我觉得应该是
Is this friendship? I think so!
我们是手镯兄弟
Check it out! We're bracelet buddies!
大家都会这样叫我们的
That's what they'll call us!
好了，拿去吧 随你什么时候还都可以
Okay,here you go. Pay me back whenever you like.
你用恐龙支票？
You have dinosaur checks?
对啊，你不但得到钱 还可以学到一点东西
You get your money and you learn something.
这有什么不对的？
What's wrong with that?
没什么…
Nothing.
你是小器龙
Hey,you're a cheap-a-saurus!
开玩笑… 谢谢，我很感激你
I'm kidding,I'm kidding. Thank you,I'm very grateful.
莫妮卡，这是什么东西啊？
Hey,Mon,what is this?
我高中时代的泳衣啊 那个时候比较胖
That's my bathing suit from high school. I was a little bigger then.
我还以为是康涅狄格州雨天用的遮雨棚呢
I thought they used that to cover Connecticut when it rains.
莫妮卡，这带子里有什么？
Hey,what's on this videotape?
不知道，问倒我了 放来看看
I don't know. Let's put it in.
这边，杰克
Over here,Jack. Okay.
瑞秋要出来了
Rachel's coming up the path.
好漂亮，是不是？
Doesn't she look pretty? Jack?
过来拍她
Can you get this?
我的天啊
Oh,my God!
你鼻子怎么回事啊？
What is with your nose?
我隔膜长歪了 不得已，只好去缩鼻了
They had to reduce it because of my deviated septum.
我错了 那才是康涅狄格州的遮雨棚呢
Okay,I was wrong. That's what they use to cover Connecticut.
知道这是什么吗？ 毕业舞会前的准备
This is us getting ready for the prom.
各位，我们不用看这个
We don't have to watch.
我们要看…当然要看
Yeah,we do.
看嘛 很好玩的
-Come on! -It's fun!
你有没有拍莫妮卡？
Get a shot of Monica.
莫妮卡在哪儿？
Where's Monica?
这里啊，老爸
Over here,Dad!
等一等，镜头怎么伸缩？
Wait. How do you zoom out?
拍到了
There she is!
那个女的吃了莫妮卡
Some girl ate Monica!
闭嘴啦，上镜头会多十磅的
Shut up! The camera adds ten pounds.
那到底有几个镜头在拍你？
So how many cameras are actually on you?
你好漂亮哦
Oh,you look so great!
你也是好美啊
So do you! You look beautiful!
糟了 怎么了？
-Oops. - What?
我想我的美乃滋沾到你了
I think I got mayonnaise on you.
没关系啦 只是肩膀，没弄到衣服啊
Oh,it's just the shoulder,not my dress.
你们笑一笑
Everybody smile!
爸，关掉啦
Oh,Dad,turn it off!
关了
It is off.
爸，你没关，那红灯亮着
It is not! What's with the red light?
那表示关了
It's the off light.
罗斯
Right,Ross?
很帅啊，科特尔先生（情景喜剧《科特尔先生归来》中的主角）
Looking good,Mr. IKotter.
你今天晚上很漂亮 谢谢
- You look pretty tonight. -Oh,thanks.
你今年夏天要做什么？ 你知道的，只是…
- What are you doing this summer? -I'm gonna hang out...
…在家里待着玩我的音乐
... work on my music.
我钩子没钩吗？ 袖子一直掉下来，没办法固定
Is my hook unhooked? These things keep falling down.
我看看，不知道
Let me see. I don't know.
今年夏天你要做…
What are you gonna do...
他们来了
The guys are here!
…什么？
... this summer?
玩你的音乐？
Work on your music?
天啊，你们看，是罗伊噶布里克
Oh,my God! There's Roy Gublik!
罗伊看星球大战看了317次
You know,Roy saw Star Wars 317 times.
他的名字还上了报
He was in the paper.
奇普呢？他为什么还没来？
Where's Chip? Why isn't he here yet?
他会来的，放心吧
He'll be here,okay? Take a chill pill.
好了
There.
我刚告诉瑞秋 罗伊摸我的咪咪
I just told Rachel that Roy touched my boob.
没男伴我去不成毕业舞会 来不及了
I can't go to the prom without a date. I can't! It's too late!
你不去，我也不要去了
If you're not going,then I don't want to go.
我要踹奇普的屁股
Oh,I'm gonna kick Chip's ass!
我有个很棒的主意
I have a wonderful idea.
你可以陪瑞秋去参加舞会啊
You should take Rachel to the prom.
我心里没谱
Doubtful.
杰克，那个给我 你跟儿子去谈一谈
Jack,give me that. Talk to your son.
这玩意儿好重
All right,go on. This thing's heavy.
你妈说得对，带她去 穿我的礼服
Your mother's right. Take her. You can wear my tux.
爸，她不会想跟我去的
She won't wanna go with me.
她当然会，你是大学生呀
Of course she would! You're a college man!
我不知道 去呀
-I don't know. - Well,come on.
你不想弄清楚吗？
Don't you wanna find out?
真不敢相信 我去不成自己的毕业舞会
I can't believe I can't go to the prom!
这太残酷了
This is so harsh!
-好，你帮我拿着 -这才是我的男孩…
-Hold my board. - Thataboy! Thataboy!
好了，各位，我想我们看够了
I think we've seen enough.
我们把它关掉吧
Let's turn it off.
那好吧，我就不看
Well,I'm not gonna watch.
来吧，孩子，我们走了
Come on,kid. Let's go!
天啊，你真帅 去给她们看看
-My! Are you handsome! -Let's show them!
等一下，爸
Just a sec,Dad.
要酷…
Okay,be cool. Just be cool.
好了，老爸
Okay,Dad.
瑞秋，准备好 你的白马王子来了
Rachel,ready or not,here comes your knight in shining
糟了
Oh,no.
别等我们回来了
Don't wait up!
走了，奇普，快
Chip!
天啊
Oh,dear!
杰克，这个怎么关啊？
How do I turn this off?
按按钮
Press the button.
哪个钮…？
Which one? Which button? Jack!
那个啦…
The button! The button!
真不敢相信你那么做了
I can't believe you did that.
是呀…
Yeah,well....
瞧，他是她的龙虾
See? He's her lobster!
跟他跳
Dance with him!
妈，我饿了
Mom,I'm hungry!
跟你爸跳
Dance with your father.
我或许不会跳什么闪舞啦 不过我也绝不是个门外汉
I don't know any of your flashdances,but I'm no slouch on the dance floor.
好吧
All right.
-哦，杰克 -哦，茱蒂
-Oh,Jack! -Oh,Judy!